Tomorrow is the fifth day
What should we do
Anyone here, boss
I'm coming in
Boss
I see the forest frogs in your farm
Are a bit thin
Who are you
No trespassing on the farm
Get out
Boss
This is our newly developed
special frog feed
Gains 10 grams in three days
Give it a try
Money-back guarantee
28.7 grams
Up 2 grams from yesterday
This feed really works
I'll buy it
I'll buy it all
Boss
Lewes's secret recipe
I figured it out
Boss
It's only been three days
Gained a full 13 grams
13 grams in three days
15 days left before Walter visits
At this rate
We can definitely beat Lewes
Great
Jason
I knew I picked the right guy
From now on
The whole farm
Will switch to your secret feed
Secure Walter's 10-million order
I'll give you top credit
Boss
Rest assured
With me here
Walter's 10-million order
Is definitely yours